{
  "extraDescription": "for squares of 0-20 and roots in 0-20",
  "randomQuestionCount": 5,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "4&sup2;",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "9&sup2;",
      "answer": "81"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{49}\\)",
      "answer": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "17&sup2;",
      "answer": "289"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{256}\\)",
      "answer": "16"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{324}\\)",
      "answer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "15&sup2;",
      "answer": "225"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{289}\\)",
      "answer": "17"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{4}\\)",
      "answer": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{121}\\)",
      "answer": "11"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{196}\\)",
      "answer": "14"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{81}\\)",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "19&sup2;",
      "answer": "361"
    },
    {
      "question": "2&sup2;",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "13&sup2;",
      "answer": "169"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{100}\\)",
      "answer": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{9}\\)",
      "answer": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{400}\\)",
      "answer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{36}\\)",
      "answer": "6"
    },
    {
      "question": "1&sup2;",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "5&sup2;",
      "answer": "25"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{144}\\)",
      "answer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{169}\\)",
      "answer": "13"
    },
    {
      "question": "18&sup2;",
      "answer": "324"
    },
    {
      "question": "7&sup2;",
      "answer": "49"
    },
    {
      "question": "6&sup2;",
      "answer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "11&sup2;",
      "answer": "121"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{0}\\)",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "0&sup2;",
      "answer": "0"
    },
    {
      "question": "20&sup2;",
      "answer": "400"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{1}\\)",
      "answer": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{16}\\)",
      "answer": "4"
    },
    {
      "question": "16&sup2;",
      "answer": "256"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{225}\\)",
      "answer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{64}\\)",
      "answer": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "12&sup2;",
      "answer": "144"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{25}\\)",
      "answer": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "\\(\\sqrt{361}\\)",
      "answer": "19"
    },
    {
      "question": "3&sup2;",
      "answer": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "8&sup2;",
      "answer": "64"
    },
    {
      "question": "14&sup2;",
      "answer": "196"
    },
    {
      "question": "10&sup2;",
      "answer": "100"
    }
  ]
}
